<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on James Le Nguyen</title>
    <link>https://ikellog.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on James Le Nguyen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ikellog.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>learning curve</title>
      <link>https://ikellog.github.io/posts/learningcurve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikellog.github.io/posts/learningcurve/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve read blog post and articles about programming and having now personally experiencing it&amp;ndash;there is definitely a learning curve but like with anything new you learn&amp;ndash;it will be hard at first; move forward and you will be rewarded with new insight and knowledge. And more importantly if you have any self-doubt, find people who can support your learning endevors.(this applies to any subject)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python is fun</title>
      <link>https://ikellog.github.io/posts/pythonisfun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikellog.github.io/posts/pythonisfun/</guid>
      <description>In my younger days when I was playing around with the windows command prompt, I remember seeing python in the OS directory but never thought twice what it was or why it was installed—I just figured it was something that made Windows XP work. It&amp;rsquo;s not until now that I noticed everything connecting and the relation to things that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t notice before which feels both interesting and somewhat regreftul. Also, did I mention programming is hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Hero&#39;s Journey</title>
      <link>https://ikellog.github.io/posts/aherosjourney/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikellog.github.io/posts/aherosjourney/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll start this post with a generic but hopfully motivational quote:
 &amp;ldquo;Life is full of missed opportunities, especially if you don&amp;rsquo;t try, you&amp;rsquo;ll never know what thoes possibilities could be.&amp;quot;&amp;mdash;unknown
 I&amp;rsquo;ve been working full-time since the completion of my bachelor’s back in 2012 and its funny to think that the only thing I wanted then, was to work. Now, having worked for all these years&amp;mdash;school wasn’t so bad (minus the lack of $).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>